# Drew K Goodin

dkg@fastmail.com | 650.307.5479 | SF Bay Area | https://drewgoodin.github.io

### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Multi-faceted professional with experience from carpentry to database administration. I have a special affinity for working with large log files and data sets, using command line and scripting tools to extract information and make sense of complicated things. I enjoy anything that can be turned into a math problem and am open to any career path that challenges me.

#### **EDUCATION**

PURDUE UNIVERSITY | BS MATHEMATICS

West Lafayette, IN

### WORK EXPERIENCE

### THE WINDOW TAILOR | Sales / Install Mgr - California Greater Bay Area | January 2021 - Present

- In-home sales & design consults for high-end window treatments (shades and shutters)
- · Work with vendors, suppliers, and customers daily to deliver highest level of service
- · All web development / server admin, marketing and social media

#### VIGILENT INC | Technical Support Engineer Oakland, CA / Remote | March 2020 - November 2020

- Support the deployment and use of very technical AI-based software related to building automation and HVAC
- First line of response for JIRA tickets and customer phone calls
- · Provide and document solutions directly or triage to engineering
- Develop internal tools for engineering productivity, infrastructure, and documentation
- Manage internal test Virtual Machines (VMWare / Ubuntu)

# MASSEY'S WOODWORKS / DREW GOODIN GUITAR CABINETRY | Carpenter Dallas, TX - Bay Area, CA | Januaru 2016 - March 2020

- · Began in the trade on a carpentry crew building decks, arbors, and fences
- Promoted to a shop woodworker milling stock and fabricating parts for fine furniture
- · Eventually founded and ran my own business building selling high end speaker enclosures

# PALO ALTO MEDICAL FOUNDATION | HRIS SPECIALIST Mountain View, CA / Burlingame, CA | March 2012 - November 2015

- Develop database queries, both GUI-based and pure SQL, for the purpose of HR data reports and analysis
- Ensure integrity and data standard compliance of all edits and new entries to personnel data across 7000+ employees and several physical sites
- Serve as Help Desk for all HR related information systems including timekeeping (Kronos) and HRMS (Lawson)

## **CORE SKILLS**

Office Suite / Data Tools

Google cloud suite, Advanced Excel skills

ADVANCED COMPUTING
WEB DEVELOPMENT

Linux / command line administration, MySQL / MariaDB, Perl programming

Grav CMS, Jekyll, Wordpress / WooCommerce

### OTHER EMPLOYMENT

### HALF MOON BAY GOLF LINKS, 2011-19, SEASONAL

Assistant golf professional / golf shop associate. Involved in all aspects of guest experience; sales, reservations, tournament organization.